buildquizzes.com 2019-05-17

# Security and Privacy Settings at Do Quizzes

## Introduction

Do Quizzes is committed to protecting your privacy and the privacy of your quiz takers. We will never sell, misuse or exploit any information provided to us. We collect information for the sole purpose of improving the range of tools we provide. Our privacy policy explains how we collect and treat this information. By using our services you acknowledge that you have reviewed and accepted the terms of our privacy policy. 

This privacy policy does not apply to separate entities utilizing the services of Do Quizzes. 

## Information Collection

The following describes the types of information collect during various interactions with our services.

### Account Information

During either Facebook or form account registration with Do Quizzes we may collect personally identifying information such as IP address, First, Last name and more. 

### Respondent Information

We collect information such as IP, location, timing and website visitor metrics in order to provide both security and reporting features to quiz creators. We also use engagement metrics in order to deliver the most popular content to our website visitors. 

### Advertisements

Sometimes our quizzes contain ads served via the Google Adsense network. Google adsense may use information on our site in order to serve the most relevant ads to quiz users. 

## Security

### Preventing automated voting

We employ several evolving digital fingerprint technologies which monitor voter trends. In addition to this unusual responses on large quizzes are flagged and reviewed manually. To this end we collect IP address, browser, referrer and other details which help us to evaluate the authenticity of a response and evaluate trends. The technology behind our voting abuse system remains private. There are several levels of security which may be adjusted by our content creators depending upon their unique requirements. 

### Information Storage

We store collected information in a secure SQL database and make every effort to ensure security against vulnerabilities. As with any web based platforms there are risks involved in transmitting information and while we undertake considerable effort to ensure security we cannot provide absolute assurance and so we encourage all users to exercise discretion when providing personal information. 

## Further Information

Quizzes deemed to be offensive, illegal or defamatory may be removed at our sole discretion. If you have a complaint about a specific poll or quiz please contact us via the link below and make sure you send us the link. 

Should you require further clarification or have a suggestion in regards to our privacy policy please do not hesitate to get in contact with us
